Would you like a chocolate?
(Penny:)Um, yeah, sure.
(Penny:)Thanks.
(Leonard:)What was that?
(Sheldon:)You said be nice to Penny.
(Sheldon:)I believe offering chocolate to someone
falls within the definition of "nice."
(Leonard:)It does. But in my experience, you don't.
(Sheldon:)There are more things in heaven
and Earth, Horatio...
(Sheldon:)...than are dreamt of in your philosophy.
(Leonard:)Yeah, now, that's you.
Obnoxious and insufferable.
(Howard(arriving, in goth gear):)What's going on, day dwellers?
(Penny:)Oh, man, did the KISS Army repeal
"Don't ask, don't tell"?
No. Raj and I are going to a goth club
in Hollywood...
(Howard:)...to hang with the night people.
Wanna come along?
(Penny:)Oh, wow, you're actually going out
like that?